https://www.thebereancall.org/content/privacy-policy-0

Skip to main content
HomeApostasy UpdateGet Biblical UnderstandingTBC TodaySubscribeNewsletterEnglishSpanishGermanAudioPrintableRadioBooksVideoPodcastsTopicsAll TopicsAntichristApostasyBibleCalvinismCatholicismChrist's ReturnCreation and EvolutionEmerging ChurchEnd TimesEntertainmentEternal SecurityEvangelismHebrew RootsIslamIsraelLoving GodMormonismMysticismOccultismPersecutionPrayerProphecyPsychologySalvationSeeker FriendlyThe GospelYogaAboutHistoryMission StatementStatement of FaithDave HuntT.A. McMahonDonationsHelpStoreSearch and BrowseBerean BitesBooksBook DownloadsAudio DownloadsDVDDVD for OutreachOctober Featured ProductsNovember Featured ProductsDecember Featured Products
Search form
Home Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
January 1, 2020.
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.thebereancall.org and The Berean Call and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to The Berean Call include www.thebereancall.org, TBC, The Berean Call Store and store.thebereancall.org. The TBC website is a Non-Profit site. By using the TBC website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, TBC may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:
-    First and Last Name
-    Mailing Address
-    E-mail Address
-    Phone Number
-    Email Preferences
If you purchase TBC's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction.
We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) sending us an email message; (c) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Use of your Personal Information
TBC collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
TBC may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from TBC and its affiliates.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
TBC does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
TBC may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to TBC, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
TBC may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on TBC or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of TBC; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of TBC, or the public.
Tracking User Behavior
TBC may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within TBC, in order to determine what TBC services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within TBC to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Automatically Collected Information
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by TBC. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the TBC website.
Use of Cookies
The TBC website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize TBC pages, or register with TBC site or services, a cookie helps TBC to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same TBC website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the TBC features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the TBC services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
TBC secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. TBC uses the following methods for this purpose:
-    SSL Protocol
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.
Children Under Thirteen
TBC does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
E-mail Communications
From time to time, TBC may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from TBC or click on a link therein.
If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from TBC, you may opt out of such communications by clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE button.
External Data Storage Sites
We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.
Changes to this Statement
TBC reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.
Contact Information
TBC welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that TBC has not adhered to this Statement, please contact TBC at:
The Berean Call
PO Box 7019
Bend, Oregon 97702
Email Address:
customerservice@thebereancall.org
Telephone number:
541-382-6210
Effective as of January 02, 2020
Media Library
Keep in Touch!
Click here to see our updated Privacy Policy
There are quite a few options for keeping in touch with us:
Email Options
Subscribe to our email updates here, and choose if you want daily, weekly, or monthly updates.
The Berean Call Mobile App
Most of our content is published in our app for iOS, Andoid, Windows, and Kindle.  Click here to get the app!
Parler:
https://parler.com/profile/thebereancall
Facebook:
https://www.facebook.com/thebereancall/
Twitter:
https://twitter.com/thebereancall
Instagram:
https://www.instagram.com/thebereancall/
Youtube:
https://www.youtube.com/user/TheBereanCall/videos
Livestream:
https://livestream.com/bereancallconference
Vimeo:
https://vimeo.com/thebereancall
Podcasts:
Apostasy Update (iTunes)
Apostasy Update (Google)
Apostasy Update (Amazon)
TBC Podcast (iTunes)
TBC Podcast (Google)
TBC Podcast (Amazon)
Get Biblical Understanding (iTunes)
Get Biblical Understanding (Google)
Get Biblical Understanding (Amazon)
What Love is This? (iTunes)
What Love is This? (Google)
What Love is This? (Amazon)
Mind Invaders (iTunes)
Mind Invaders (Google)
Mind Invaders (Amazon)
Newsletter Podcast (Amazon)
Paper Options
The Berean Call is available by postal mail each month for free.  We are willing to send the newsletter to you by regular mail but encourage you to read it online to save printing and mailing costs. Send us a message to add or change your paper mail address.
The Berean Call is also available in a large-print edition at a nominal cost.
If you are outside the U.S. The Berean Call is available by paid subscription .
Copyright © The Berean Call 2016. All rights Reserved.  Click here for copyright permissions.
Blog
Home
